Holland
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Holland
2.1.1.1.10
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1184
- Holland, 2.1.1.1.10
  - Near the railroad bridge, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 17; 3001; 55; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Grote Kerk or Church of Saint Lawrence, canal and railroad bridge, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 18; 3004; 42; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Leaning house and old style architecture, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 19; 3005; 40; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Statue of poet Hendrik Tollens, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 20; 3007; 107; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Statue of Erasmus, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 21; 3008; 100; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Showing sign for baker and Thomson's pudding, Rotteram, circa 1915; 22; 3009; 98; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - On the Boompjes, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 23; 3132; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Bridge at Boompjes, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 24; 3136; 167; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Bridges at Boompjes, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 25; 3010; 80; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - The Boompjes, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 26; 3011; 72; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Railroad bridge over Mass River (Meuse River), Rotterdam, circa 1915; 27; 3013; 66; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Along a canal, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 28; 3138; 144; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Burgermeister's house, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 29; 3016; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Residence, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 30; 3018; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - In the business section, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 31; 3019; 61; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Bit[?] in Rotterdam, circa 1915; 32; 3131; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Old windmill in city, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 33; 3133; 220; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Fine Residence, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 34; 3134; 231; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Chimneys, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 35; 3137; 166; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Park scene, Rotterdam, circa 1915; 36; 3135; 130; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Park in Rotterdam, circa 1915; 37; 3139; 163; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Wash day, Rotterda, circa 1915; 38; 3140; 284; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Windmill, Delfshaven, circa 1915; 39; 3148; 199; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Artistic house, Delfshaven, circa 1915; 40; 3150; 156; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Point of departure of Pilgrim Fathers, Delfshaven, circa 1915; 41; 3149; 190; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Grote Kerk (cathedral), Dordrecht, circa 1915; 42; 3020; 108; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Street scene, Dordrecht, circa 1915; 43; 3141; 339; 4x5 film (Box 1184)
  - House, Dordrecht, circa 1915; 44; 3142; 338; 4x5 film (Box 1184)
  - Woman with headdress, Dordrecht, circa 1915; 45; 3143; 336; 4x5 film (Box 1184)
  - Canal, Dordrecht, circa 1915; 46; 3144; 330; 4x5 film (Box 1184)
  - City gate, Dordrecht, circa 1915; 47; 3145; 328; 4x5 film (Box 1184)
  - Up a canal, Dordrecht, circa 1915; 48; 3146; 168; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Canal bit[?], Dordrecht, circa 1915; 49; 3147; 145; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Oude Kerk (old church),Tomb of Admiral Maarten van Tromp, Delft, circa 1915; 50; 3021; 103; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Nieuwe Kerk (new church), Memorial to William the Silent, Frank R. Roberson in foreground, Delft, circa 1915; 51; 3022; 102; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Nieuwe Kerk (new church), showing statue of religion in memorial to William the Silent, Delft, circa 1915; 52; 3023; 93; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Nieuwe Kerk (new church), tomb of Hugo Grotius, Delft, circa 1915; 53; 3024; 88; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Nieuwe Kerk (new church), Delft, circa 1915; 54; 3153; 346; 4x5 film (Box 1184)
  - Nieuwe Kerk (new church), william the Silent and dog, Delft, circa 1915; 55; 3025; 65; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Portrait of William the Silent, circa 1915; 56; 3026; 296; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Door of Prinsenhof, Delft, circa 1915; 57; 3027; 302; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  - Oude Kerk (old church), leaning tower, Delft, circa 1915; 58; 3028; 291; 5x7 (Box 1184)
  Box 1185
- Holland, 2.1.1.1.10
  - Spot where William the Silent was murdered, Delft, circa 1915; 1; 3029; 292; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - City gate, Delft, circa 1915; 2; 3154; 329; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Soldiers, Delft, circa 1915; 3; 3151; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Woman selling fish, Delft, circa 1915; 4; 3152; 347; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Street scene, The Hague, circa 1915; 5; 3218; 193; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Canal scene, The Hague, circa 1915; 6; 3030; 54; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Hall of the Knights in Binnenhof, The Hague, circa 1915; 7; 3031; 52; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - States General building, The Hague, circa 1915; 8; 3217; 345; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Spuistraat, The Hague, circa 1915; 9; 3032; 50; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - National monument(1869), The Hague, circa 1915; 10; 3033; 113; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Passage, The Hague, circa 1915; 11; 3034; 97; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Interior of Grote Kerk(cathedral), with queen's seat, The Hague, circa 1915; 12; 3035; 122; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Grote Kerk(cathedral), where queen attends, the Hague, circa 1915; 13; 3036; 86; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Gevangenport(old prison), The Hague, circa 1915; 14; 3221; 157; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - House of Spinoza, The Hague, circa 1915; 15; 3037; 73; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Houses showing various styles of architecture, The Hague, circa 1915; 16; 3038; 63; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - The queen's palace, The Hague, circa 1915; 17; 3039; 74; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Statue of William the Silent in the plein, The Hague, circa 1915; 18; 3040; 60; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Long path in Het Bosch, near House in the Wood, The Hague, circa 1915; 19; 3041; 124; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - In Het Bosch, The Hague, circa 1915; 20; 3043; 114; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Het Bosch, The Hague, circa 1915; 21; 3044; 111; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Canal in Het Bosch, queen's skating canal, The Hague, circa 1915; 22; 3045; 77; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Wedding carriage, The Hague, circa 1915; 23; 3219; 196; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Funeral procession, The Hague, circa 1915; 24; 3220; 185; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Queen Emma(copy of a photograph), circa 1915; 25; 3047; 357; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Queen of Holland(copy of a photograph), circa 1915; 26; 3048; 294; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Queen Wilhelmina of Holland and prince consort, circa 1915; 27; 3049; 305; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Portrait of Queen Wilhelmina of Holland, circa 1915; 28; 3050; 299; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Paul Potter's "The Young Bull", The Hague, circa 1915; 29; 3052; 293; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Interior of large department store, The Hague, circa 1915; 30; 3053; 303; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Road to Scheveningen, The Hague, circa 1915; 31; 3046; 89; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Kurhaus(casino) Scheveningen, circa 1915; 32; 3054; 128; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Group of Dutch boys, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 33; 3222; 332; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Frieslanders, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 34; 3223; 137; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Headdress, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 35; 3224; 136; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Street, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 36; 3225; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Street scene, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 37; 3226; 252; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Street, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 38; 3227; 267; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Tiny house, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 39; 3228; 271; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - People digging on beach at Scheveningen, circa 1915; 40; 3229; 272; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Woman in chair sitting next to movie camera on beach at Scheveningen, circa 1915; 41; 3229A; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Group on beach at Scheveningen, circa 1915; 42; 3230; 274; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Beach, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 43; 3231; 279; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Promenade wagon, Scheveningen, circa 1915; 44; 3232; 194; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Bathing wagon at Scheveningen, circa 1915; 45; 3233; 275; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - House of Peter the Great, Zaandam, circa 1915; 46; 3055; 112; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Houses built in church, Haarlem, circa 1915; 47; 3173; 278; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Bridges and old houses, Haarlem, circa 1915; 48; 3175; 251; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Flower garden, Haarlem, circa 1915; 49; 3170; 331; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Gladiolas, near Haarlem, circa 1915; 50; 3171; 283; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Gladiolas, near Haarlem, circa 1915; 51; 3172; 183; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Flowering begonia, circa 1915; 52; 3169; 334; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Street leading to Amsterdam Gate, Haarlem, circa 1915; 53; 3174; 273; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Amsterdam gate, Haarlem, circa 1915; 54; 3176; 236; 4x5 film (Box 1185)
  - Grote Kerk(cathedral), meat market, Kermesse buildings, Haarlem, circa 1915; 55; 3064; 290; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Meat market, Haarlem, circa 1915; 56; 3057; 87; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Stadhuis(town hall), Haarlem, circa 1915; 57; 3058; 92; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Statue of Laurens Coster, Haarlem, circa 1915; 58; 3059; 99; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Interior of cathedral showing large organ, Haarlem, circa 1915; 59; 3060; 118; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Interior of cathedral, ship decoration, Haarlem, circa 1915; 60; 3061; 115; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - View over city from cathedral, Haarlem, circa 1915; 61; 3062; 95; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - View from cathedral, Haarlem, circa 1915; 62; 3063; 45; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  - Road to Leyden, circa 1915; 63; 3164; 286; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Road to Leyden, circa 1915; 64; 3167; 138; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Road near Leyden, circa 1915; 65; 3165; 139; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Road nearby Leyden, circa 1915; 66; 3166; 140; 4x5 (Box 1185)
  - Main street showing stadhuis(town hall), Leyden, circa 1915; 67; 3067; 83; 5x7 (Box 1185)
  Box 1186
- Holland, 2.1.1.1.10
  - Stadhuis(town hall), Leyden, circa 1915; 1; 3068; 39; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - The ruins of "The Burg", Leyden, circa 1915; 2; 3069; 82; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - University gymnasium, Leyden, circa 1915; 3; 3159; 197; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Soldiers, Leyden, circa 1915; 4; 3168; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Dutch soldiers, Leyden, circa 1915; 5; 3160; 195; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Van der Werf Monument, Leyden, circa 1915; 6; 3161; 189; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Railroad sign, Leyden, circa 1915; 7; 3162; 141; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Sidewalk obstruction, Leyden, circa 1915; 8; 3163; 142; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Dufot[?] drawbridge, railroad station and canal, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 9; 3179; 171; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Railroad station, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 10; 3070; 84; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Church of St. Nicholas and Schreierstoren (Tower of Tears) from the harbor, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 11; 3071; 126; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Schreierstoren (Tower of Tears), Amsterdam, circa 1915; 12; 3183; 149; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - The Bourse, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 13; 3072; 57; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Royal Palace, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 14; 3073; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Royal Palace, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 15; 3074; 48; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Binnen-Amstel, Sophia Plein, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 16; 3075; 47; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Amstel Hotel and bridge, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 17; 3180; 162; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Montelbaanstoren Tower, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 18; 3076; 41; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Shipping in harbor, from government tower, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 19; 3077; 96; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Fishing boats in Amsterdam, circa 1915; 20; 3182; 147; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Fish market and old weigh house, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 21; 3078; 90; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Post office, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 22; 3079; 75; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Achterburgwal, Jewish quarter, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 23; 3184; 150; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Street in Jewish quarter, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 24; 3186; 287; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Achterburgwal, Jewish quarter, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 25; 3187; 151; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Death announcer, circa 1915; 26; 3177; 160; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Ridder Straat, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 27; 3185; 288; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Oude Kerk (old church), Amsterdam, circa 1915; 28; 3181; 143; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Rembrandt Plein, theater, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 29; 3188; 134; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Rijksmuseum, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 30; 3178; 225; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Head of Rembrandt, by himself, circa 1915; 31; 3080; 295; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Rembrandt’s “Syndics”, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 32; 3082; 308; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Rembrandt’s “Night Watch”, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 33; 3083; 309; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - “Celebration of the Peace of Munster” by Bartholomeus van der Helst, Amsterdam, circa 1915; 34; 3084; 335; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Stern of boat on canal, circa 1915; 35; 3085; 307; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Windmills and canal, road to Broek, circa 1915; 36; 3086; 81; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Windmill and house, road between Amsterdam and Broek, circa 1915; 37; 3088; 85; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Night scene, road from Amsterdam to Broek, circa 1915; 38; 3189; 203; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Tiny house, Broek, circa 1915; 39; 3190; 260; 4x5 film (Box 1186)
  - Interior of house, showing beds, Broek, circa 1915; 40; 3089; 120; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Canal scene, Edam, circa 1915; 41; 3090; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Canal view, Edam, circa 1915; 42; 3246; 155; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Weighing cheeses in warehouse, Edam, circa 1915; 43; 3091; 116; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Interior of cheese warehouse, Edam, circa 1915; 44; 3092; 91; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Dam Hotel in Edam, circa 1915; 45; 3245; 356; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Pigs in the rain, Edam to Zaandam, circa 1915; 46; 3244; 210; 4x5 (Box 1186)
  - Weigh house, Alkmaar, circa 1915; 47; 3093; 110; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Old castle, Muiden, circa 1915; 48; 3094; 79; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Hunebed, Rolde, circa 1915; 49; 3095; 56; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  - Old gate (1578), Hoorn, circa 1915; 50; 3096; 43; 5x7 (Box 1186)
  Box 1187
- Holland, 2.1.1.1.10
  - Weigh house, Hoorn, circa 1915; 1; 3097; 109; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Fourteenth century decoration of house in honor of naval victory, Hoorn, circa 1915; 2; 3098; 78; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Leaning houses, Grote Oost, Hoorn, circa 1915; 3; 3234; 224; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Row of buildings, Hoorn, circa 1915; 4; 3235; 218; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Dog cart, Hoorn, circa 1915; 5; 3236; 214; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Weighing cheeses, Hoorn, circa 1915; 6; 3237; 200; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Tree decoration, Hoorn to Enkhuizen, circa 1915; 7; 3240; 229; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - House decoration, road between Hoorn and Enkhuizen, circa 1915; 8; 3243; 154; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Colored doll houses, road from Hoorn to Enkhuizen, circa 1915; 9; 3108; 68; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Drommedaris Tower, 1540, Enkhuizen, circa 1915; 10; 3107; 64; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Great lock from Zuiderzee, Enkhuizen, circa 1915; 11; 3109; 51; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Interior, Marken, circa 1915; 12; 3099; 123; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Isle of Marken from the sea, circa 1915; 13; 3192; 208; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Women of Marken, circa 1915; 14; 3193; 234; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Woman washing, Marken, circa 1915; 15; 3194; 246; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Girls with hay boats, Marken, circa 1915; 16; 3197; 219; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Roberson in automobile, windmill, circa 1915; 17; 3198; 184; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Child with long pole, Marken, circa 1915; 18; 3199; 177; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Baby with a can, Marken, circa 1915; 19; 3200; 179; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Small child with mother, Marken, circa 1915; 20; 3201; 209; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Five children on bench, Marken, circa 1915; 21; 3202; 249; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Children near harbor, Marken, circa 1915; 22; 3203; 266; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Two little children, Marken, circa 1915; 23; 3204; 264; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Women in street, Marken, circa 1915; 24; 3205; 129; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Main street, Marken, circa 1915; 25; 3206; 132; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Row of houses, Marken, circa 1915; 26; 3207; 135; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Near boat landing, Marken, circa 1915; 27; 3208; 191; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Houses near boat landing, Marken, circa 1915; 28; 3209; 265; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Along the Zuiderzee, showing dykes and land below sea level, circa 1915; 29; 3100; 301; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Boats on the Zuiderzee, near Volendam, circa 1915; 30; 3101; 127; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Fishing boats, Volendam, circa 1915; 31; 3102; 58; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Woman and child, Volendam, circa 1915; 32; 3103; 94; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Woman and child in headdress, Volendam, circa 1915; 33; 3104; 49; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Women on road, Volendam, circa 1915; 34; 3210; 247; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Women walking, Volendam, circa 1915; 35; 3211; 176; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Man with wide trousers, Volendam, circa 1915; 36; 3212; 204; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Old man and dyke, Volendam, circa 1915; 37; 3213; 169; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Man in costume, Volendam, circa 1915; 38; 3214; 133; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - People standing near fence, Volendam, circa 1915; 39; 3215; 205; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Group around automobile, Volendam, circa 1915; 40; 3216; 206; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Lifting bridge on canal, Volendam, circa 1915; 41; 3105; 44; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Along the dyke, Volendam, circa 1915; 42; 3106; 70; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Grote Markt, Groningen, circa 1915; 43; 3110; 125; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - University church, Groningen, circa 1915; 44; 3111; 104; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - University library, Groningen, circa 1915; 45; 3112; 71; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Library of university, Groningen, circa 1915; 46; 3113; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Town hall, Groningen, circa 1915; 47; 3260; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Old watch tower, Groningen, circa 1915; 48; 3261; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - On road to Zwolle, circa 1915; 49; 3285; 270; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Milk buckets and tubs, on road to Zwolle, circa 1915; 50; 3115; 76; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Houses in country, Zwolle, circa 1915; 51; 3286; 241; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Country houses near Zwolle, circa 1915; 52; 3287; 238; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Children near Zwolle, circa 1915; 53; 3288; 221; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Children on road to Zwolle, circa 1915; 54; 3289; 222; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Street in Zwolle, circa 1915; 55; 3290; 175; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Lock basin at Zwolle, circa 1915; 56; 3291; 172; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Apothecary sign, Zwolle, circa 1915; 57; 3114; 53; 5x7 (Box 1187)
  - Rhenen, on road to Utrecht, circa 1915; 58; 3262; 187; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Fine residence on road to Utrecht, circa 1915; 59; 3270; 213; 4x5 (Box 1187)
  - Statue of John van Nassau, Utrecht, circa 1915; 60; 3263; 281; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Cathedral tower, Oudegracht (old canal), Utrecht, circa 1915; 61; 3264; 348; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Scene in park, Utrecht, circa 1915; 62; 3265; 349; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Canal scene, Utrecht, circa 1915; 63; 3266; 351; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Old houses, 1651, Utrecht, circa 1915; 64; 3267; 352; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Nieuwegracht (new canal), Utrecht, circa 1915; 65; 3268; 353; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  - Old canal (Oudegracht), in Utrecht, circa 1915; 66; 3269; 354; 4x5 film (Box 1187)
  Box 1188
- Holland, 2.1.1.1.10
  - Street scene, Utrecht?, circa 1915; 1; 3271; 159; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Cathedral tower, Utrecht, circa 1915; 2; 3272; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - General view showing housetops, Utrecht, circa 1915; 3; 3116; 119; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Road to Arnhem showing hills, circa 1915; 4; 3279; 180; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Postkantoor (post office), Arnhem, circa 1915; 5; 3117; 106; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Massive architecture, Arnhem, circa 1915; 6; 3118; 105; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - High school, Arnhem, circa 1915; 7; 3119; 67; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Stadhuis (town hall), Arnhem, circa 1915; 8; 3274; 215; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Glass front to house, Arnhem, circa 1915; 9; 3275; 212; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Soldier’s home, Arnhem, circa 1915; 10; 3277; 182; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Music Sacrum, Arnhem, circa 1915; 11; 3278; 187; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Park, Arnhem, circa 1915; 12; 3280; 158; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Canal, Schiedam, circa 1915; 13; 3126; 333; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Street, Schiedam, circa 1915; 14; 3127; 211; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Old woman sewing, Schiedam, circa 1915; 15; 3128; 198; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Modern hat on headdress, Schiedam, circa 1915; 16; 3129; 350; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Children and musician, Schiedam, circa 1915; 17; 3130; 146; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Sand dunes at Zandvoort, circa 1915; 18; 3155; 276; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Little boy at Zandvoort, circa 1915; 19; 3156; 250; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Residence, Zeist, circa 1915; 20; 3157; 344; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Small residence, Zeist, circa 1915; 21; 3158; 280; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Street, Monnickendam, circa 1915; 22; 3247; 263; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Automobile at Monnickendam, circa 1915; 23; 3248; 259; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Street in Monnickendam, circa 1915; 24; 3249; 216; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Street scene, Monnickendam, circa 1915; 25; 3250; 161; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Park in Apeldoorn, circa 1915; 26; 3273; 114; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Palace at Het Loo, circa 1915; 27; 3281; 178; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Avenue of trees leading to Het Loo Palace, circa 1915; 28; 3282; 148; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Palace of Het Loo, queen’s summer residence, circa 1915; 29; 3284; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Pig from market, Leeuwarden, circa 1915; 30; 3283; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Weigh house, Leeuwarden, circa 1915; 31; 3252; 226; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Cattle market, Leeuwarden, circa 1915; 32; 3253; 223; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Apple woman, Leeuwarden, circa 1915; 33; 3254; 258; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Old woman in Friesland helmet, circa 1915; 34; 3255; 257; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Cattle market, Leeuwarden, circa 1915; 35; 3256; 256; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Cattle from market, Leeuwarden, circa 1915; 36; 3257; 245; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Street Leeuwarden, circa 1915; 37; 3258; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Automobile and people, Leeuwarden, circa 1915; 38; 3259; 228; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Women washing, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 39; 3292; 340; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Women, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 40; 3293; 341; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Child, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 41; 3294; 342; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Small child, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 42; 3295; 152; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Crowd of children, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 43; 3296; 282; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Women and children, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 44; 3297; 343; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Crowd around automobile, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 45; 3298; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Boats near houses, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 46; 3299; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Group around doorway, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 47; 3300; 165; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Women and children, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 48; 3301; 170; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Children, Spakenburg, circa 1915; 49; 3302; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Group of Dutch boys, circa 1915; 50; 3125; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Small boat at sea, circa 1915; 51; 3251; 289; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Dog cart (one dog), circa 1915; 52; 3304; 235; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - On a country road, circa 1915; 53; 3305; 254; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Church on country road, circa 1915; 54; 3306; 248; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Canal bit, sailboat, circa 1915; 55; 3307; 239; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Canal scene on country road, circa 1915; 56; 3308; 242; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Cows, circa 1915; 57; 3309; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Cows, circa 1915; 58; 3310; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Cows, circa 1915; 59; 3311; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Moving houses, circa 1915; 60; 3312; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Storks on roof of house, circa 1915; 61; 3313; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Pasture scene, sheep, circa 1915; 62; 3314; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - House decoration, circa 1915; 63; 3315; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - House decoration, circa 1915; 64; 3316; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Sail set in woods, circa 1915; 65; 3317; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Sail in fields, circa 1915; 66; 3318; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Sail in fields, circa 1915; 67; 3319; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Woman drawing sailboat, circa 1915; 68; 3320; 4x5 film (Box 1188)
  - Sail in the field, circa 1915; 69; 3321; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Sailboat on canal, circa 1915; 70; 3322; 4x5 (Box 1188)
  - Dutch scene (copy), circa 1915; 71; 3120; 358; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Woman with Friesland helmet, circa 1915; 72; 3121; 359; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Canal and house (copy), circa 1915; 73; 3122; 360; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Boats on the Zuiderzee (copy), circa 1915; 74; 3123; 361; 5x7 (Box 1188)
  - Dutch boat (copy), circa 1915; 75; 3124; 362; 5x7 (Box 1188)